drgolfstore.com 2011-09-18

# Privacy Notice _ Service Center _ Help _ golf clubs store online _ golf clubs store online

This Privacy Notice describes how we treat personal information when you buy and enjoy Drgolfstore' products and services, including information provided since you register at our site.

At Drgolfstore.com, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect when you use our products and services, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience.

We have 5 privacy principles that describe how we approach privacy and user information across all of our products:

1\. Use information to provide our users with valuable products and services.

2\. Develop products that reflect strong privacy standards and practices.

3\. Make the collection of personal information transparent.

4\. Give users meaningful choices to protect their privacy.

5\. Be a responsible steward of the information we hold.

This Notice was created to provide you with easy-to-understand information about our products and policies to help you make more informed choices about which products you buy, how to use them and what information you provide to us.

You need a Drgolfstore Account which asks for some personal information when you create an Account, including your alternate contact information and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. This Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.

Drgolfstore.com stores, processes and maintains your messages, contact lists and other data related to your account in order to provide the service to you.

You can feel free to buy products from us privately.
